Snehil Tripathi

Nottingham, 07495514968, snehil030@gmail.com

PROFILE	Dedicated researcher with 5+ years of treatment & academic experience within the field of clinical psychology. Adept in applying research skills in the area of addiction. Experienced in supporting individuals with personality disorders. Committed to inform clinical practice and research initiatives.	
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
Jul 2019 — Feb 2020	Mental Healthcare Assistant, Nottingham Brain Injury Rehabilitation Centre	Nottingham
	Assisted individuals with a wide range of cognitive impairments post brain injury. Supported all aspects of physical and mental well-being.	
Jan 2019 — Jul 2019	Mental Healthcare Assistant, Elysium	Newark
	Collaborated with the health care team to establish and manage patient care for patients with personality disorder, psychosis & schizophrenia.	
Jul 2017 — Jan 2018	Healthcare Assistant, Constance Care	Sterling
	As a care worker, I worked with disabled, mentally ill and terminally ill elderly. My duties included providing personal assistance with a variety of daily tasks including personal grooming, meal preparation, feeding and light housework.	
May 2017 — Jan 2018	Teacher, Hospital education department at Royal Hospital for Children	Glasgow
	I volunteered at the Royal Hospital for Children as a primary level teacher. My responsibilities were to educate children (between the ages of 5 and 12) under a prescribed curriculum to promote their intellectual growth.	
May 2017 — Jan 2018	Volunteer, Alzheimer Scotland	Glasgow
	In my position as a volunteer, my primary job responsibility was to provide personalised sup with Dementia. My duties included befriending and supporting with day-to-day activities.	port to individuals
Oct 2015 — Aug 2016	Trainee Researcher, C.C.M. Medical College and Hospital	Bhilai
	My duties involved gathering primary data and producing research reports during clinical trials of a potential new medicine.	
EDUCATION		
Oct 2018 — Aug 2022	MPhil, University of Nottingham	Nottingham
	Graduated from University of Nottingham with an MPhil in Clinical Psychology with the hopes to continue to a PHD at a later date. My study was based around Cannabis dependency of which I am in the process of being published.	
Oct 2016 — Oct 2017	MSc Psychological Studies, University of Glasgow	Glasgow
	Graduated with a Master's in Psychological Studies with the dissertation focusing on the role subjective well-being.	e of religiosity on
Oct 2012 — Oct 2015	BA (Hons), Sharda University	Delhi
	Graduated with a Bachelor of Arts (Honours) in English Literature with a distinction grade	
REFERENCES	Mark Petho from Elysium	

pethomarko@icloud.com · +44 7425 581319

Katy Jones from University of Nottingham

mczkj@exmail.nottingham.ac.uk

Musa Sami from University of Nottingham

mszmbs@exmail.nottingham.ac.uk